<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>新型化学电笔微盒</title>
  
  <subtitle>东厦中学</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://EnrichK.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2019-07-18T15:57:00.270Z</updated>
  <id>https://EnrichK.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>EnrichK</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Use the Instruction Manual</title>
    <link href="https://EnrichK.github.io/2017/11/04/translate2/"/>
    <id>https://EnrichK.github.io/2017/11/04/translate2/</id>
    <published>2017-11-03T17:14:57.000Z</published>
    <updated>2019-07-18T15:57:00.270Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<script src="\assets\js\APlayer.min.js"> </script><p>The new chemical pen microbox as a teaching instrument is designed to help students understand the concept of electrolyte, non-electrolyte, strong electrolyte and weak electrolyte.</p><p>The product can be replaced by two kinds of display devices, such as optical display and magnetic display. The delicate electrolytic bottle is prepared by the proper concentration of various typical electrolytes. The independent development of solid electrolytic tube has achieved the objective of testing the conductive capability after the class demonstration of low temperature solid melting. The whole set of equipment is small, and the experiment is miniaturized to win more time and space for teachers.</p><a id="more"></a><p><strong>一、Product Appearance Image</strong></p><p><img src="http://a4.qpic.cn/psb?/V11n71CD3DWf6r/XMt2ZColTYl03FycSzF5JOLbDL.9yA8JbfhkmZO.AEo!/m/dPMAAAAAAAAAnull&amp;bo=LQLYAAAAAAADB9U!&amp;rf=photolist&amp;t=5" alt=""></p><p><strong>二、Use the Instructions</strong></p><p>The product can be realized:</p><ul><li><p>Determination of electrolyte and non-electrolyte;</p></li><li><p>Determination of strong and weak electrolytes;</p></li><li><p>To determine the three functions of molten state solid electrolyte conductivity.</p></li></ul><p><img src="http://a3.qpic.cn/psb?/V11n71CD3DWf6r/SqRxskIhQlMRffR7YzcUUDeSoTTB4lKY9mbSX2s7TnM!/m/dPIAAAAAAAAAnull&amp;bo=hwDAAAAAAAADB2U!&amp;rf=photolist&amp;t=5" alt=""></p><p>1．Determination of electrolyte and non-electrolyte;</p><p>（1）Put the battery into the battery bin of the pen, cover the battery cap, and switch the top block.</p><p>（2）Light Display: insert the interface of the pen into the optical display device, and the interface of the pen is connected with the liquid electrolyzer. If the light is illuminated, the liquid is electrolyte solution; If the light display device is not bright, the liquid is non-electrolyte.</p><p>（3）Magnetic Display: keep the switch position unchanged, remove the optical display device and insert the interface of the pen into the magnetic display device. At this point, the moving switch is in the middle (empty reset) to the lower block, and the electromagnet is put into the iron powder. If the reducing iron powder is adsorbed, the liquid is electrolyte solution; If the reducing iron powder is not adsorbed, the liquid is non-electrolyte.</p><p>（4）After use, remove the parts and wipe them clean and put them back to the microbox for use.</p><p>2．Determination of strong and weak electrolytes</p><p>（1）Put the attery into the battery bin of the pen, cover the battery cap, and switch the top block.</p><p>（2）Light Display: Insert the interface of the pen into the optical display device, and the interface of the pen is connected with the liquid electrolyzer. If the light is in blue and green, the liquid is a weak electrolyte solution; If the light is in the white area, the liquid is a strong electrolyte solution.</p><p>（3）Magnetic display: keep the switch position unchanged, remove the optical display device and insert the interface of the pen into the magnetic display device. At this point, the moving switch is in the middle (empty reset) to the lower block, and the electromagnet is put into the iron powder. If adsorption obviously adsorption, the liquid is a strong electrolyte solution; The liquid is a weak electrolyte or non-electrolyte if the adsorption of the iron powder is not obvious adsorption.</p><p>（4）After use, remove the parts and wipe them clean and put them back to the microbox for use.</p><p><img src="http://a4.qpic.cn/psb?/V11n71CD3DWf6r/5CiYFnL3HqD6x*aGhkZmPI5C9rXMN3abGHtvEyzzjFE!/m/dPMAAAAAAAAAnull&amp;bo=3QD5AAAAAAADBwY!&amp;rf=photolist&amp;t=5" alt=""></p><p>3．Determination of solid electrolyte conductivity of molten state</p><p>（1）Put the battery into the battery bin of the pen, cover the battery cap, and switch the top block.</p><p>（2）Connect the interface of the pen with the light display section, insert the interface of the pen into the solid electrolytic tube adapter and rotate clockwise until it is locked.</p><p>（3）Open the air cover on both sides of the solid electrolytic tube and hook the handle to the fixed button on the solid electrolyte to parallel the handle of the handle to the table.</p><p>（4）Place the bottom of the solid electrolysis tube at the bottom of the alcohol lamp for two minutes, and the solid is completely melted. This time display device is bright, and the conductivity of the solid electrolyte is judged according to the number of the light bulb.</p><p>（5）After use, remove the parts and wipe them clean and put them back to the microbox for use.</p><p><strong>三、Attention Matters</strong></p><p>1．Please switch the switch to the middle stop after the use of the pen. If it is not used for a long time, the battery should be taken out.</p><p>2．When the solid electrolysis tube is heated, please pay attention to fire safety and stop heating in half a minute after solid melting.</p><p>3．Liquid electrolysis bottle should not be inverted long term. If not used for a long time, the solution should be poured out and cleaned.</p><blockquote><p>If you want to know more, please click <a href="https://v.qq.com/x/page/t0567fadf24.html&quot;化学电笔演示实验&quot;" target="_blank" rel="external">here</a> to watch the demo experiment.</p></blockquote>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;The new chemical pen microbox as a teaching instrument is designed to help students understand the concept of electrolyte, non-electrolyte, strong electrolyte and weak electrolyte.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The product can be replaced by two kinds of display devices, such as optical display and magnetic display. The delicate electrolytic bottle is prepared by the proper concentration of various typical electrolytes. The independent development of solid electrolytic tube has achieved the objective of testing the conductive capability after the class demonstration of low temperature solid melting. The whole set of equipment is small, and the experiment is miniaturized to win more time and space for teachers.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="研究性学习" scheme="https://EnrichK.github.io/tags/%E7%A0%94%E7%A9%B6%E6%80%A7%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A0/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>HP2131打印机</title>
    <link href="https://EnrichK.github.io/2017/11/04/translate1/"/>
    <id>https://EnrichK.github.io/2017/11/04/translate1/</id>
    <published>2017-11-03T17:14:52.000Z</published>
    <updated>2019-07-18T15:58:38.844Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<script src="\assets\js\APlayer.min.js"> </script><p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/bao/uploaded/i1/TB1zFOvKFXXXXcGXXXXXXXXXXXX_!!0-item_pic.jpg" alt=""></p><p><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1087328833/O1CN01BGmqh42F7Yx6yZUry_!!1087328833.jpg" alt=""><br><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i1/1087328833/O1CN01GXMMbs2F7YwoLXaLK_!!1087328833.jpg" alt=""><br><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i4/1087328833/O1CN0157MPyG2F7YzVWbqYv_!!1087328833.jpg" alt=""><br><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i2/1087328833/O1CN01ZdgXET2F7YwoFStPt_!!1087328833.jpg" alt=""><br><img src="https://img.alicdn.com/imgextra/i3/1087328833/O1CN01MUmTNa2F7YvmHDGRT_!!1087328833.jpg" alt=""></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;script src=&quot;\assets\js\APlayer.min.js&quot;&gt; &lt;/script&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.alicdn.com/bao/uploaded/i1/TB1zFOvKFXXXXcGXXXXXXXXXXXX_!!0-item_p
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="研究性学习" scheme="https://EnrichK.github.io/tags/%E7%A0%94%E7%A9%B6%E6%80%A7%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A0/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
